Guide to the Ron Padgett Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 2009 Acquistion, 1929-2008; (89 boxes)
  - Correspondence, 1950s-2008
    - Vermont, 1965-2004
      - Correspondence Received, 1990; 6 (Box 22)
        Includes approximately 225 letters and postcards from:
        Louis Simpson
        Gunnar Harding
        James Schuyler
        Jerome Rothenberg
        Douglas Oliver
        Miriam Cendrars
        Bob Homan
        Elmore Leonard
        Kathleen Fraser
        Ed Friedman
      - Correspondence Received (continued), 1990; 2 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence Received, 1991; 3 (Box 23)
        Includes 1 Ron Padgett letter, as well as approximately 70 other letters and postcards from various people:
        Richard Hell
        Steve Vincent
        Paul Slovak
        Mary Ann Caws
        Basil King
      - Correspondence Received, 1992-1993; 6 (Box 23)
        Includes approximately 250 letters and 120 postcards from:
        Edith Schloss
        John Martin
        Keith Waldrop
        Wang Ping
      - Correspondence Received (continued), 1992-1993; 2 (Box 24)
      - Letters, Cards, Etc., 1994; 7 (Box 24)
        Includes approximately 200 letters and postcards from:
        Mark Polizzotti
        Anselm Berrigan
      - Letters, Cards, Etc., 1994 (Box 24)
        These folders include approximately 250 letters and postcards from:
        Sharon Olds
        Roy Blount Jr.
      - Letters, Cards, Etc. (continued), 1994; 7 (Box 25)
      - Correspondence, Boxed, 1995; 5 (Box 25)
        Carol Bergé
        Susan Wheeler
        Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
      - Correspondence, Boxed (continued), 1995 (Box 26)
      - Mail Received, Vermont, 1996-2000; 6 (Box 26)
        Lorenzo Thomas
        Jennifer Dorn
        Frank André Jamme
        Juliet Clark
        Rachel Hadas
        Jonathan Williams
      - Vermont Correspondence, Sent and Received, 1989-2002; 5 (Box 26)
        Includes approximately 150 letters from Ron Padgett, as well as 150 letters and postcards from:
        Kit Robinson
        Christopher Edgar
        Jonathan Galassi
        Michael Heller
        Louise Glück
        Billy Collins Serge Fauchereau
        Matthew Rohrer
        Charles Simic
      - Vermont Correspondence, Sent and Received (continued), 1989-2002; 2 (Box 27)
      - Postcards Received, 1965-1970; 9 (Box 27)
        Includes approximately 600 postcards from:
        Man Ray
        Samuel R. Delaney
        Arthur A. Cohen
        Edward Gorey
        Lawrence Ferlinghetti
        Paul Carroll
        Miriam Patchen
        Lauren Owen
        George Tysh and Chris Tysh
        Steve and Mary Carey
        Le Harwood
        Rolf Dieter Brinkmann
        Betty Kray
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1970-1975; 2 (Box 27)
        Includes approximately 400 letters and postcards from:
        Paol Keineg
        F.W. Dupee
        Ray di Palma
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received (continued), 1970-1975; 7 (Box 28)
      - Miscellaneous Letters Received, 1973; 4 (Box 28)
        Includes approximately 10 to 15 Ron Padgett letters, as well as 250 letters and postcards from:
        Charles Reznikoff
        George Plimpton
        Rebbecca Brown
        Cid Corman
        Ruth Krauss
      - Micellanous Letters Received (continued), 1973 (Box 29)
      - Letters To and From Ron Padgett, 1979; 3 (Box 29)
        Includes 24 letters from Ron Padgett, as well as 50 letters and postcards from:
        Joan Ludman
        Veronica Geng
        Barrett Watten
        Jon Simon
      - Miscellaneous Letters and Papers Received, 1969, 1974-1980; 4 (Box 29)
        Includes documents related to Ron Padgett's 1974 California reading tour, the Poetry Project, the Teachers & Writers Project Newsletter. Also included are 10 letters from Ron Padgett, as approximately 50 postcards and letters from:
      - Letters, 1980-1983; 4 (Box 29)
        Includes approximately 65 letters from Ron Padgett, as well as 200 letters and postcards from:
        David Budbill
        Red Smith
        Richard Kostelanetz
      - Letters (continued), 1980-1983; 2 (Box 30)
      - Correspondence Received, 1982; 5 (Box 30)
        Philippe Soupault
        Eliot Weinberger
        Ada Katz and Alex Katz
        David Wilk
      - Vermont Correspondence - In and Out, 2003-2004; 2 (Box 30)
        Includes approximately 18 letters from Ron Padgett, as well as 75 letters from:
        Rachel Blau du Plessis
        Oddfridur Rasmussen
        Tom Devaney
        Jody Gladding
        Cedar Sigo
        David Hinton
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1977-1995
      - Living Room Top Shelf - Ron Padgett Letters, 1984-1990; 3 (Box 30)
      - Ron Padgett Letters and ETS Letters and Papers, 1977-1979; 6 (Box 31)
        Includes Ron Padgett letters, dating from September 1977 to September 1979, as well as ETS letters and papers regarding a planning panel for the National Arts Award. Also included are approximately 300 handwritten notes.
      - Ron Padgett Letters [Manhattan Ministorage], 1979-1982; 6 (Box 31)
      - Correspondence from Ron Padgett [Manhattan Ministorage], 1991-1995; 3 (Box 31)
  - Writings, 1930-2006
    - Poems in Spiral Notebooks, 1963-1968; 4 (Box 32)
    - Radio Research paper, 1973 (Box 32)
      Includes post college papers, notes from the early 1960s, as well as a copies of letters from Ron Padgett to Leroy Breunig and Pascal Pia, and other material.
    - Conversations with Marcel Duchamp, 1960s-1970s (Box 32)
    - Grosse Feuerballe manuscript, 1970-1971 (Box 32)
    - Tulsa Kid, 1979; 2 (Box 32)
    - Kitaj article, 1970 (Box 32)
    - Poetry manuscripts requested by Holt, 1970 (Box 32)
    - File folder with poems and notes, 1970s (Box 32)
    - Antlers in the Treetops, 1970s (Box 32)
    - List of Corrections, 1973 (Box 33)
    - RE: Antlers in the Treetops GRIST (Box 33)
    - The Poems of A.O. Barnabooth (Box 33)
    - In Advance of the Broken Arm, 1964 (Box 33)
    - Strange Faeces #3 (Box 33)
    - Creative Reading manuscript, 4 (Box 33)
    - Ceravolo proofs, 1991-1992; 3 (Box 33)
    - Edwin's Tao proofs, 1993 (Box 33)
    - Among the Blacks proofs, 1985-1988; 2 (Box 33)
    - Bloodwork Proofs, 1992-1993; 7 (Box 34)
    - Version of TED, 1991-1993; 7 (Box 34)
    - New Yorker, 1981-1984 (Box 34)
    - Larbaud Translations, notebooks, 1973-1975; 2 (Box 34)
    - Notes for Duchamp and Roussel lecture (Box 35)
    - Lessons in Things, 1983 (Box 35)
    - Padgett manuscripts, 1966, 1974 (Box 35)
      Includes Tlooth review draft, A Preliminary Toast, and Fill-in-the Blanks by Tessie Mitchell.
    - Larbaud (Box 35)
    - Big Something, 1979 (Box 35)
    - Long Poem (Box 35)
    - Creative Reading, 1973-1996
      - NCTE Version, 1995-1997; 4 (Box 35)
        Includes 6 computer disks
        Conditions Governing Access
        Reference copies of electronic files are available. Consult Access Services for further information.
        20090223-26062.0001:
        20090223-26062.0002: CR Figs #3
        20090223-26062.0003: Figs Disk #2
        20090223-26062.0004: Figs Disk #1
        20090223-26062.0005: Cherry 1-3
        20090223-26062.0006: Cherry 4-5
      - Notes, etc., 1992-1996; 5 (Box 35)
        Includes handwritten notes, xeroxed articles and xeroxes of figures.
      - Creative Reading - Notes and Sources, circa 1974-1987; 3 (Box 36)
      - Copies and Page Proofs, 1996; 4 (Box 36)
      - Creative Reading - Figures and proofs, 1973, 1989-1996; 4 (Box 36)
    - The Poet Assassinated, 1968 (Box 37)
    - Toujour L'Amour, 2 (Box 37)
    - Great Balls of Fire, binder, 1964-1969 (Box 37)
    - Big Blue Jay Compositions (Box 37)
    - Great Balls of Fire, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
    - Examples of College Papers, 1961-1962 (Box 37)
    - Poems Rejected by Holt, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Triangles in the Afternoon, 1979 (Box 37)
    - Tulsa Kid, copy, 1979 (Box 37)
    - The Poet Assassinated, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Blaise Cendrars, 1948-1990; 6 (Box 37)
    - Albania Diary, 1997-1999; 4 (Box 38)
      Includes 7 computer disks
      20090223-26062.0007: Albanian Diary, 9/25/98 Final Version For the Figures
      20090223-26062.0008: Albania, MAP Frontispiece, 9/19/98
      20090223-26062.0009: Albanian Diary, 9/12/98, For the Figs
      20090223-26062.0010: Albanian Diary Covers (For the Figures)
      20090223-26062.0011: Albanian Diary, 5/98, 6/16/98 PM
      20090223-26062.0012: Albanian Diary, PM 6/16/98
      20090223-26062.0013: Albanian Diary, PM 6/16/98
    - Scribner Essays #1, 1998-1999; 6 (Box 38)
    - Scribner Essays #2, 1998-1999; 5 (Box 38)
    - Scribner Essays #3, 1998-1999; 3 (Box 39)
    - Scribner Notes, 1998; 5 (Box 39)
      Includes notes, addresses, correspondence, advisory material and preliminary submissions.
    - Scribner Notes, 1998-1999; 3 (Box 39)
      Includes lists and contracts, as well as manuscript material.
    - Daddy manuscript, 1996; 2 (Box 39)
    - Daddy manuscript, 1995; 3 (Box 40)
    - Daddy manuscript - Family Version, 1996-1997; 3 (Box 40)
    - Daddy drafts, 1994-1997; 4 (Box 40)
    - Daddy drafts, 1995-1997; 2 (Box 40)
    - Daddy drafts (continued), 1995-1997; 2 (Box 41)
    - Oklahoma Tough (big box:: master files), 1930-1997; 13 (Box 41)
      Includes clippings, FBI correspondence, notes, and xeroxes.
    - Oklahoma Tough (big box: master files) (continued), 1930-1997; 6 (Box 42)
    - Oklahoma Tough, final manuscript etc., 1996-2002; 5 (Box 42)
    - Oklahoma Tough FBI files, 1963-1994; 2 (Box 42)
    - Oklahoma Tough FBI files (continued), 1963-1994; 5 (Box 43)
    - Creative Reading: MS & source material, 1988-1989; 3 (Box 43)
    - Oklahoma Tough: final manuscript, 2004; 3 (Box 43)
      Includes 1 computer disk
      20090223-26062.0014: Oklahoma Tough
    - "Minneapolis" and "TV Conference", 2002-2003 (Box 43)
    - "Folger" and "Paris", 2004 (Box 43)
    - Oklahoma Tough - OU Marketing, 2002-2003 (Box 44)
    - Response to Oklahoma Tough, 2002-2005 (Box 44)
    - "Coffee House" and "You Never Know", 2000 (Box 44)
    - You Never Know, second proofs, 2001-2002 (Box 44)
    - Geo. Essays ER: Collab Show, 2002-2004 (Box 44)
    - Geo. Collab. Book, 2002-2003 (Box 44)
    - "EZ Wesley Tanner" and "Two Serious Gents", 1993-2003 (Box 44)
    - Scribners, 1999 (Box 44)
    - University of Michigan, 1988-2000 (Box 44)
    - Michigan manuscript, 1998-2000 (Box 44)
    - Submissions, 1988-2002 (Box 44)
    - "Visual Works for Tulsa Kid" and "Writing Summer", 1981-1982 (Box 44)
    - Writing Summer, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
    - "Writing", 1983-2001; 11 (Box 45)
      Includes various "Vermont" manuscripts by Ron Padgett.
    - "Prose Collabs" and "Dick's Account of Branson Trip", 1960, 1990 (Box 46)
    - MSS letters, notes, etc.- by Ted, Dick Ron, etc., 1959-1965 (Box 46)
    - "Misc MSS", 1975 (Box 46)
    - Writing at Civitella R., 2003 (Box 46)
    - Writing: Summer, 1980-1981 (Box 46)
    - Poems - Lancaster, 1976-1977 (Box 46)
    - NYC, 1978-1980 (Box 46)
    - Poems - Summer 1975 (Box 46)
    - Poems, 1974 (Box 46)
    - 1972-1974 1972-1974 1972-1974 (Box 46)
    - "Better Poems" and "Revised and Reprinted", 2005-2006 (Box 46)
    - Revisions - Group 1 & Group 2, 1996-2006 (Box 46)
    - New Revisions, 1991-2005 (Box 46)
    - CHP manuscript - first rough cut, 2005 (Box 46)
    - CHP manuscript - second version, 2006 (Box 46)
    - VT 2001, 1999-2001 (Box 47)
    - "VT 1998" and "VT 1999", 1998-1999 (Box 47)
    - Stock Car Racing (Box 47)
    - "For Talk at New College", 1995 (Box 47)
    - Ted - best version so far, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Ted - draft, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Ted, 1990-1999; 2 (Box 47)
    - Earlier version of Ted, 1991 (Box 47)
    - Motor Maids original (Box 47)
    - "Pantoum", binder, 1983-1984 (Box 47)
    - Full Court Press photos (Box 47)
    - Full Court Press (Box 47)
    - Star Gut, binder (Box 47)
    - Full Court Press letters, 1974, 1976 (Box 47)
    - Translation Festival, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Reid Hall, 1981 (Box 47)
    - The Little Car, 1978 (Box 47)
    - The Sad Sadness (Box 47)
    - Motor Maids Across the Continent, 2 (Box 48)
    - Anthology of NY Poets (Box 48)
    - Anthologized Poets, 4 (Box 48)
    - NY Poets - Bios and Biblios (Box 48)
    - The Whole Word Catalogue, 5 (Box 48)
    - Great Balls of Fire, 1984-1990 (Box 48)
    - Great Balls of Fire, 1984-1990; 4 (Box 49)
    - Household Words, 1985; 2 (Box 49)
    - The Big Something (Box 49)
      Includes works that were removed from "Household Words" to create "The Big Something".
    - The Big Something (Box 49)
    - Selected Works (Box 49)
    - Joe: A Memoir of Joe Brainard, 2000-2004
      - Joe - commentary by Bill Berkson and Ann Lauterbach, 2003 (Box 49)
      - Joe: A Memoir of Joe Brainard, 2001 (Box 49)
      - "Joe p. 287-339 rev. 5/21/03", 2003 (Box 49)
      - Joe LIVE, 2004 (Box 49)
      - Joe Proofs - third pass, 2004 (Box 50)
      - Joe Galleys - second pass, 2004 (Box 50)
      - Joe Galleys - first set, 2004 (Box 50)
      - Joe 'Public' Version - Revised 10/2/03, 2003 (Box 50)
      - Joe 'Last Private Version' (with details included), 2003 (Box 50)
      - Joe 5/16/02, 2002 (Box 50)
      - Papers Relating to Joe Brainard: A Retrospective, the art catalogue, 2000 (Box 50)
      - Joe - Version Revised 10/11/00, 2000 (Box 51)
    - Motor Maids, 2000; 2 (Box 51)
    - The Straight Line - Michigan Proofs, 2000 (Box 51)
    - Oklahoma Tough, 1997, 2000; 2 (Box 51)
    - Grant Applications - NEA and CAPS, 1974-1981 (Box 51)
    - Edwin Denby's Complete Poems, 1965-1987 (Box 51)
      Includes poems, proofs, various correspondence, school papers, photocopies, transcripts and other material.
    - Edwin Denby's Complete Poems (continued), 1965-1987; 10 (Box 52)
    - Cendrars, 1970-1993; 2 (Box 52)
      Includes early drafts, proofs, notebooks and notes.
    - Cendrars (continued), 1970-1993; 9 (Box 53)
    - Cendrars, circa 1991 (Box 53)
      Includes material relating to Blaise Cendrars: Complete Poems.
    - Cendrars (continued), circa 1991; 8 (Box 54)
    - How To Be Perfect, 2005-2007; 4 (Box 54)
    - Poet Assassinated, 1981-1987; 4 (Box 54)
    - Poet Assassinated (continued), 1981-1987; 3 (Box 55)
    - The Big Something, 1989 (Box 55)
    - Joe, 2002 (Box 55)
    - Early Writings, 1956-1963
      - Junior and Senior High School, 1956-1960; 6 (Box 55)
      - Poems and Notebooks, 1956-1960; 2 (Box 55)
      - Poems and Notebooks, 1956-1960; 4 (Box 56)
      - Dreams, 1960-1962 (Box 56)
      - Poems, 1960-1963 (Box 56)
      - "Z", 1960s (Box 56)
        Contains a manuscript made up of only the letter Z.
      - Miscellaneous Old Manuscripts, 1960s; 5 (Box 56)
    - Writings by Others, 1967-1998
      - Basketball Diaries, 1995-1998; 3 (Box 56)
      - Serge Fauchereau, 1983-1991 (Box 56)
      - Serge Fauchereau (continued), 1983-1991; 3 (Box 57)
      - Miscellaneous Manuscripts by Others and Mags, 1979-1993; 7 (Box 57)
      - Manuscripts by Others, 1967-1982; 6 (Box 57)
      - Manuscripts by Others, 1969-1970; 2 (Box 58)
    - Ted Berrigan, 1965-1994
      - Paris Review, 1966-1994 (Box 58)
      - Ted manuscript, 1968-1970 (Box 58)
      - Bean Spasms, 1965-1981 (Box 58)
      - Ron's Book, 1968 (Box 58)
      - "Bean Spasms" and "Ron's Book" (Box 58)
    - Other Writings, 1974-2006
      - Revised Hopefuls, 2004 (Box 58)
      - Revisions Group 1, 2004-2006 (Box 58)
        Includes unpublished manuscripts and revised poems.
      - Manuscripts to Refile, 1992-2006 (Box 58)
        Includes material labeled: "The poems that sat on my desk".
      - VT 1995, 1984-1996 (Box 58)
        Includes collaborative project notes with Hans Hokansen, as well as manuscript material relating to "The Big Something".
      - Published Pieces, 1974-1976 (Box 58)
      - LOA manuscripts, 2002-2006; 5 (Box 59)
  - Notebooks and Bokes, 1963-2005
    - Notebooks, 1963-1972
      - 6x8 excercise book, circa 1968-1969 (Box 59)
      - 5x8 notebook containing notes from Gino Severini La Vita Di Un Pittore, circa 1965 (Box 59)
      - 7x9 excercise book containing writings on Braque and Reverdy, circa 1965 (Box 59)
      - Excercise book containing drawings by Ron Padgett and Pat Padgett (Christmas), circa 1965 (Box 59)
      - 9x6 book containing poems and drawings, circa 1969 (Box 59)
      - 10x7 notebook containing typed inserts, notes, peoms and translations, circa 1963 (Box 59)
      - 8x10 notebook containing Jarry's Ubu Bound by Ron Padgett, circa 1963 (Box 59)
      - 8x10 notebook used for essay on Joe Brainard's 12 work. (Box 59)
      - 8x10 spiral notebook containing poems and drawings, circa 1971 December - 1972 April (Box 59)
      - "Little Anthology of NC Ministories", typed (Box 59)
      - "The Bingo", with handwritten comments. (Box 59)
    - Back in Boston, Again, 1970s (Box 59)
      Contains 3x4 handwritten notebook which includes tickets and maps which have been folded into the book.
    - Notebook, circa 1979 (Box 59)
      Contains 3x4 handwritten notebook which contains library notes and first drafts of various 1979 poems. A library slip has been folded in.
    - Notebooks and Bokes, 1964-2005
      - 6x9 notebook, "Back in Cambridge, Again" by Rond Padgett and "NC", circa 1968 (Box 60)
      - 6x5 notebook, containing magazine articles on pinball, a version of the poem "Around Paris" and some writings and notes, circa 1965-1966 (Box 60)
      - 6x8 notebook, containing notes and drawings, circa 1979-1980 (Box 60)
      - 9x7 notebook "Nine Portraits" containing poems and translations, circa 1964 (Box 60)
      - 3x5 notebook, containing notes on a trip to Paris, addresses, things to do, poems, etc., circa 1981 (Box 60)
      - 3x4 notebook, "At the Fogg". (Box 60)
      - 3x4 notebook, containing notes taken while watching "Koch play". (Box 60)
      - 4x7 notebook regarding Man Ray (Box 60)
      - Envelope with two small handwritten bokes: "fill'er up editions cartoons" and "A Boy Named George" (Box 60)
      - 4x6 notebook regarding Teaching, circa 2005 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, "The Selected Letters of Tom Clark for Ron Padgett" (Box 60)
      - "13 Tanka" by Anne Waldman for Ron Padgett's birthday, circa 1969 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke with stapled pages and carbon paper. (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, newspaper collage pages stapled ("Voice") (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, stapled "Two Stories for Andy Warhol", circa 1964 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, stapled xeroxed poems by Ron Padgett, Berkson and Brownstein. (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, "the Legend of Bingo" by Cendrars (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, stapled, for Pat, circa 1965 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Boke, plastic folder, "Invisible, Walking, Writing Light". (Box 60)
      - 8x11 "3+1" typed poems by Ron Padgett (Box 60)
      - 8x11 ledger "Picabia", circa 1964 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 plastic cover with faint xeroxes of pictures by Larry and Joan Fagin (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 8x11 page on cardboard containing a reworked cartoon by Ted Berrigan
      - 7x9 Boke, "Secret" xeroxed poems, circa 1964 (Box 60)
      - 8x11 booklet, "Early Heroes", containing drawings by Ron Padgett from grade school (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 8x11 stapled "Early Heroes" with illustrations cut from books (circa 1960s)
      - 7x10 Boke, "Cup", containing words and drawings, circa 1964 (Box 60)
      - Bat Man Comic with new words by Ron Padgett (Box 60)
      - 5 loose pages of comic strips redone by Sandy Berrigan (Box 60)
      - 4x4 stapled xeroex of Paris Review form letters (Box 60)
      - 11x5 booklet with paintings, "A Man Saw A Ball of Gold", circa 1966 (Box 60)
      - 5x7 spiral notebook, "Predict Ted's Recovery" (Box 60)
      - 7x8 booklet used by Ron Padgett on his 1979 trip to Holland, circa 1979 (Box 60)
      - 6x6 Boke, containing typed poems, circa 1968 (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 6x8 Boke, "To a Schuyler" (circa 1967)
      - 8x11 Binder, "Manoroid", by Tom Veitch (Box 60)
      - 8x11 Binder, "The Ron Padgett Story" by Tom Veitch (Box 60)
      - 4x6 Birthday Book for Ron Padgett by Schneeman and Brownstein, circa 1970s (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 3x5 Boke, "Various Small Fires" by Tom Veitch and One page newspaper, "The Naked Express".
    - Bokes by Ron, 1960s-1970s
      - 6x9 Boke, "Foto-rama" (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 6x9 Boke, "Toad Poems" by Tom Veitch; 6x8 Boke, stapled xerox of "Toad Poems"; 6x8 Boke, "Europe" (circa 1971); 5x6 Boke, typed with inscription from Peter Schjeldahl (circa 1965).
      - "Sky", printed (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 5x9 Boke, "Fifty & Seventy-Five Years Ago", made up of 1891 and 1916 news clippings; 6x8 Boke, "Ron's Hospital Poem" by Tom Dsich; 5x9 Chinese book with photos of Clarks, Anne Waldman, Lewis Warsh, Joan Fagin and Larry Fagin.
      - 6x8 Boke, stapled xeroxes by A. Saroyan and T. Clark, circa 1967 (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 8x7 music notebook with Lee Crabtree; 6x8 Boke of original edition of Apollinaire's "Julie ou la Rose"; 7x10 Boke, "Unicap", collage by Berkson.
      - 3x6 Boke containing misc notes, lists, lines and addresses, circa 1966 (Box 60)
        This folder also includes: 9x7 Boke, stapled by Steve Carey; 10x6 Valentine Day Boke by Brainard and Elmslie; The Joe Brainard Art Chronicle; "Dig the Streets", by Ron Padgett, as told by Ted Berrigan (circa 1965).
    - Notebooks, 1970s-1980s
      - Notebook with first draft translation of Phillippe Soupault, circa 1981 (Box 61)
        This folder also includes: Handwritten book by Morrie Warshawski; Notebook of Dutch Paintings; Notebook of Kitaj article with newspaper clippings (circa 1970).
      - Notebook of London Lithgraphs, circa 1970s (Box 61)
        This folder also includes: Notebooks with handwritten translations of conversations with Marcel Duchamp.
      - Red binder with xeroxed language lessons and drawings by George Schneeman (Box 61)
    - Bokes, etc., 1967-1990
      - 3x4 Blue Windows boke by Tom Clark, circa 1970s (Box 61)
        This folder also includes: Boke made up of three Blue Photos by Anne Waldman (circa 1973); Folder with two photos (circa 1972); {Driving Thru}, notebook (circa 1971).
      - 8.5x11 boke, European Diary by Anne Waldman, circa 1967 (Box 61)
      - "All that Gas" boke by Berkson and Schneeman, circa 1969 (Box 61)
        This folder also includes: New Years "card" by Berkson; Letter from Berkson (circa 1990) and "Biotherm" manuscript.
      - Berkson letter and copy of manuscript intro, circa 1989 (Box 61)
        Thsi folder also includes: "A Little Treasury of Modern Criticism", by Berkson.
      - Clark Coolidge, poem for Ron Padgett (Box 61)
        This folder also includes: Bernadette Mayer letter and poem (circa 1985); Clark Coolidge, pages from the Porter House for Ron Padgett (circa 1970); Ed Sanders Newsletter, Peace Eye Bookstore; Paul Violi, manuscript with handwritten notes (circa 1987).
  - White Dove Review, 1959-1972
    - Missing blank back covers, 1959-1960 (Box 61)
    - WDR correspondence and lists, 1959-1960 (Box 61)
    - WDR 1, 1958 (Box 61)
      Includes a typed layout of the White Dove Review with handwritten notes.
    - WDR 2, 1959 (Box 61)
      Includes a typed layout of the White Dove Review with lists and handwritten notes.
    - WDR 3, 1959 (Box 61)
      Includes a typed layout of the White Dove Review with handwritten notes from Ginsberg and Kerouac
    - WDR 4, 1960 (Box 61)
    - WDR 5, 1960 (Box 61)
      Includes a typed layout of the White Dove Review with signed manuscripts by Sorrentino, Ron Padgett, Berrigan, Creeley, LeRoi Jones, Dick Gallup and others.
    - Prospectus, 1964, 1972 (Box 61)
  - Full Court Press, 1929, 1971-1992